# HANS OLIVEIRA

+1 (647) 879 3948 | hansnery@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/hansnery/ | Toronto, ON GitHub: https://github.com/hansnery | Portfolio: https://hansnery.github.io/portfolio/

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Full-stack Developer with nearly 4 years of coding experience, a team-oriented approach, and a passion for software, web, and game development. Eager to apply and expand my technical skills in an internship/co-op. Exceptional problem-solving abilities and excellent communication skills.

# **SKILLS HIGHLIGHTS**

Ruby On Rails	SQL, PostgreSQL, and MongoDB	Self-starter
Python	NodeJS, Express JS, and React	Self-learner
Javascript	Bootstrap, Bulma and Tailwind	Communicative
Java	Modding and Game Development	Team Player
PHP	Adobe Photoshop	Persistent

# **EDUCATION**

**Diploma / Computer Programming**, Georgian@ILAC, Toronto, ON. Sep 2022 – Apr 2024

**BA in International Relations**, Unisul, Florianópolis, Brazil. Aug 2012 – Dec 2015

### **EXPERIENCE**

**Educational Support for Software Development (Co-op)** 

Aug 2023 - Present

Georgian@ILAC

Toronto

- Offer individualized support to students on programming projects through one-on-one sessions and peer programming, aiding in troubleshooting, concept comprehension, skill enhancement, and portfolio development.
- Develop and lead workshops, delivering presentations to students to foster essential skills such as proficiency in version control software, frameworks, and algorithms.
- Spearheaded the launch of Georgian@ILAC's inaugural Computer Programming Lab, independently developing foundational processes to enhance student skill sets and facilitate portfolio building.

Legislative Assembly of the State of Santa Catarina Florianópolis, Brazil

- Created and designed digital content, including graphics and videos, to enhance the Congressman's online presence and increase engagement with constituents.
- Handled the Congressman's social media profiles, informing the public of public policies, important bills and promoting key initiatives.
- Contributed to the Congressman's re-election campaign, witnessing an increase in votes from 38,547
  to 71,185 during my tenure.

# **Customer Success Consultant Intern**

Jul 2015 - Mar 2016

H2App (Start-up for delivery of bottled water and cooking gas) Florianópolis

- Led the onboarding process for new users onto the company's software, providing comprehensive guidance, training, and support to ensure a smooth transition.
- Actively supported existing users, addressing inquiries, troubleshooting issues, and offering tailored assistance to enhance their experience with the software.
- Analyzed user feedback and collaborated with the product development team to implement feature improvements.

## **MAIN PROJECTS**

## **Denison Roof Experts Website**

- Technologies used: PHP for the Backend and Tailwind CSS for the Frontend.
- **Description:** Created a website for a roofing company based in Toronto.
- **Outcome:** Modernized the client's outdated web presence, resulting in improved user experience and increased engagement metrics.
- Link: Denison Roof Experts

#### The Bugger

- Technologies used: Ruby On Rails, Bulma, and PostgreSQL. Deployed on Heroku.
- **Description:** A mock social media platform for developers inspired on Facebook.
- Outcome: Implemented features such as authentication, timeline, friending, liking and commenting.
- Link: The Bugger

## Age of the Ring: Realms in Exile

- **Technologies used:** LUA, Blender, and Adobe Photoshop.
- Description: A mod for Electronic Art's strategy game The Lord of the Rings: Battle for Middle-Earth II.
- Outcome: Has over 3200 downloads and nearly 80 people on the mod's Discord server.
- Link: Age of the Ring: Realms in Exile ModDB Page